# Suyeong Park

 $\frac{suyeong@unist.ac.kr,}{github.com/euphoria0-0} \frac{suyeong.park0@gmail.com}{github.com/euphoria0-0}$ 

#### RESEARCH INTEREST

My research interests are mainly on making more trustworthy AI using collaborations of information in data and knowledge from human being. I mainly focused on estimating uncertainty on Bayesian approach, especially 'what information we need between **representativity and uncertainty** for better ML model'. Currently, I believe 'understanding an intrinsic attributes of things using our knowledge' is crucial for deploying ML models for better human-being life in a real-world. Thus, I'm currently interested in identifying **CAUSALITY** of things from our data for explainable AI while overcoming the limitations of typical ML.

# **EDUCATION**

# Ulsan National Institute of Science and Technology (UNIST)

Ulsan, Korea

Master of Science in Artificial Intelligence

Aug. 2020 - Aug. 2022

GPA: 4.15/4.3

Advisor: Prof. Kwang In Kim and Prof. Namhoon Lee

Thesis: Active Client Selection for Communication-efficient Federated Learning [Link]

Relevant Coursework: Causal Learning & Explainable AI, Reinforcement Learning, Advanced Machine Learning Topics

University of Seoul

Seoul, Korea

Bachelor of Science in Statistics and Data Science

Mar. 2015 - Feb 2020

GPA: 3.7/4.5

Relevant Coursework: Bayesian Statistics, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Time Series Analysis, Multivariate Statistics, Statistical Computing, Linear Algebra, Probability Theory, Mathematical Statistics

### EXPERIENCE

# Visiting Researcher

Jul. 2022 - Aug. 2022

Purdue University

West Lafayette, US

• Research Project: Bayesian Causal Discovery

#### Research Assistant

Aug. 2020 – Present

Machine Learning and Vision Lab, UNIST

Ulsan, Korea

• Research Projects: active learning, transfer learning, federated learning, image attribute estimation

### Intern, Data Analyst and Engineer

Mar. 2020 - Jun. 2020

Seoul Big Data Campus

Seoul, Korea

• Projects: Citizen Movement and Consumption Behaviour analysis around Seoul city

#### Intern, Data Analyst Assistant

Sep. 2019 - Feb. 2020

FSC (Financial Services Commission)

Seoul, Korea

• Projects: Data analysis using financial public data

#### Publication

### S. Park, Y. Ahn, K. Kim. Blind (keyword: Deep Active Learning, Bayesian)

In Submission., 2022

# Projects

# Visual Common Sense Through Self-supervised Learning for Restoration of Invisible Parts in Image

April 2021 – Present

Causal Learning with Artificial Intelligence

Mar. 2021 – Dec. 2021

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python, R, SQL (MySQL)

Tools: PyTorch, TensorFlow, Git, Docker, PyCharm, VSCode

Others: QGIS, Tableau, SAS

Last Updated: September 14, 2022